A MUSICAL love affair spinning throught time.
Hello Again is a music, drama, romance film directed by Tom Gustafson.
Ten lost souls slip in and out of one another's arms in a
daisy-chained musical exploration of love's bittersweet embrace.
A film adaptation of Michael John LaChiusa's celebrated musical,
originally based on Arthur Schnitzler's play, La Ronde.
Les, played by Nolan Gerard Funk.
Ruth, played by Martha Plimpton.
Leocadia, played by Sam Underwood.
Marie, played by Jenna Ushkowitz.
Alfred, played by Al Calderon.
Emily, played by Rumer Willis.
Hello Again is a 2017 American musical film directed by Tom
Gustafson and written by Cory Krueckeberg.
Based on the Off-Broadway musical of the same name by Michael John
LaChiusa, the film stars Audra McDonald, Martha Plimpton, T.
Knight, and Rumer Willis.
The interconnected story is composed of 10 vignettes that follow lonely individuals
pursuing romance across 10 different periods throughout New York City's history.
The film explores themes of sexuality, musical, based on
play or musical, sexual fantasy, love affair.
The tone is emotional.